cheapcaribbean.com 2018-10-19

# Cheap Caribbean | CheapCaribbean.com Privacy Policy

**Effective April 29, 2017**   
Thank you for visiting CheapCaribbean.com! We are concerned about and respect your privacy while visiting our web site. We want you to know CheapCaribbean.com will never sell, lease or rent your confidential information to ensure your privacy is protected. We will always endeavor to take steps to assure that any information you provide to us will remain private and secure. Please take a moment to read over our privacy policy and let us know if you have any questions or comments. **Collection of Information**  
CheapCaribbean.com will sometimes ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, occupation, and other details. Providing us your information will simply help us offer products and services that we think you'd like to hear about. **Personal Information Privacy**  
CheapCaribbean.com will take all appropriate steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to your information databases, communicating this policy statement to all CheapCaribbean.com employees and establishing and enforcing penalties for violating this statement. 

When you submit your personally identifiable information through the www.cheapcaribbean.com Site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Please see in particular, **Cookies/Automated Collection of Information and Third Party Policies below** in this policy, to understand more.

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will use the information you provide us only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or in connection with the service for which you provided such information. For example, if you opt-in to our e-mail alert, we may use your e-mail address to send you periodic e-mails. We may forward your contact information and inquiry to our affiliates and other divisions of our company that we feel can best address your inquiry or provide you with the requested service. We may also use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may share or transfer such non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees, agents and partners.

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include, without limitation, customer support and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that coordinate mailings). Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

In addition, we may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal proceeding or governmental request. 

If he/she does not verify his/her information in the one-email invitation, we will remove this information from our database. 

**Newsletters**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. **Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. **Data Retention**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. **Security**  
CheapCaribbean.com currently uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to safeguard your information, including your credit card number, during online transactions. None of the people who have made purchases through CheapCaribbean.com's web site using SSL have reported fraudulent use of their credit card as a result of their online order. We believe SSL to be a very safe encryption method, but we are always looking for even more secure encryption methods to safeguard information sent online. **Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**  
We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please use our [contact form](http://www.cheapcaribbean.com/onlineCustomerServiceForm.jsp). **Cookies/Automated Collection of Information and Third Party Policies**  
CheapCaribbean.com currently uses "cookies" on our site. Our cookies tag each visitor's browser with a random, unique number. The cookie simply assigns a number and does not disclose any personal information about the person using the browser. By noting where these uniquely numbered browsers go on our site, we can study traffic patterns and site usage, and improve our site to better fit our customers' needs. 

We use service providers to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use these cookies to identify sources and patterns of traffic on our site. 

We may connect information collected automatically with information we already have about you in order to identify you as a CheapCaribbean.com guest, including from third parties (for example, Google Analytics, to whom you have given permission for this purpose. This allows us to provide you with a personalized experience regardless of how you interact with us online, in store, mobile, etc.

We and our service providers, and third parties you have given permission to, may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer or mobile device. This information, which includes, but is not limited to: the pages you visit on our site, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, purchase information and checkout process, search terms, and IP-based geographic location, helps us recognize you, customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. This includes CheapCaribbean.com content presented on another website or mobile application, for example, CheapCaribbean.com emails. These technologies also enable us to provide features such as storage of items in your cart. We also use Flash cookies for fraud prevention purposes.

_Interest-Based Advertising_  
CheapCaribbean.com participates in interest-based advertising (IBA), also known as Online Behavioral Advertising. We use third-party advertising companies to display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online. CheapCaribbean.com adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) self-regulatory principles for IBA.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our websites. This information is used to serve ads for CheapCaribbean.com products or services or for the products or services of other companies when you visit this website or other websites. These companies use non-personally-identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, hardware/software information, cookie and session ID) and personally identifiable information (e.g., static IP address) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These parties typically use a cookie, web beacon or other similar tracking technologies to collect this information.

**our do-not-track policy**  
Some browsers have a "do not track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser "do not track" signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of interest-based advertising. To learn more about IBA or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit [here ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/)and [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/). 

**social media** CheapCaribbean.com engages with customers on multiple social media platforms (e.g., Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest). If you contact us on one of our social media platforms, request guest service via social media or otherwise direct us to communicate with you via social media, we may contact you via direct message or use other social media tools to interact with you. In these instances, your interactions with us are governed by this privacy policy as well as the privacy policy of the social media platform you use.

_Social Media Widgets_  
Our sites and mobile applications include social media features, such as Facebook Like button, Google Plus, Pinterest, YouTube, Instagram, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you're visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

_Social Media Ads_ We may display CheapCaribbean.com ads to you through social media platforms. These ads are sent to groups of people who share traits, such as likely commercial interests and demographics. For example, we may CheapCaribbean.com guests who have expressed an interest in shopping for Cancun vacations, all-inclusive vacations, etc. We do not share any of your personal information, including your shopping history, with social media platforms. See the policies of each social media platform for additional information about these types of ads.

**how is your information shared?**  

**service providers**  
We may share the information we collect with companies that provide support services to us (such as, analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center/chat providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, or fraud prevention providers) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions.

**legal requirements**  
We may disclose information we collect when we believe disclosure to governmental authorities or other parties is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our guests or others.

**what choices do you have?**  

**email**  
If you do not wish to receive promotional emails from us, send an email to email@e.cheapcaribbean.com to opt out. You may still receive select emails from us if you have requested them through one of our services such as Weekly Ad Reminders. You can discontinue these emails by canceling your subscription to these services.

You also have the ability to unsubscribe from promotional emails via the opt-out link included in each promotional email.

**cookies, tracking & interest-based advertising**  
The help function of your browser should contain instructions on how to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued or to not receive cookies at any time. If you set your device to not receive cookies at any time, certain personalized services cannot be provided to you, and accordingly, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our features (i.e. you will be able to browse the site, but will not be able to make a purchase).

_Interest-Based Advertising_  
To opt out of interest-based advertising, visit [here ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/) and [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/). 

_Other Website Analytics Services_  
Analytics services such as Site Catalyst by Adobe Analytics and Google Analytics provide services that analyze information regarding visits to our websites and mobile applications. They use cookies, web beacons and other tracking mechanisms to collect this information.

  * To learn about Adobe Analytics privacy practices or to opt out of cookies set to facilitate reporting, click [here](http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html).
  * To learn more about Google's privacy practices, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).
  * To access and use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**California Residents**   
If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to CheapCaribbean.com Corporation, Attn: California Shine the Light Inquiry, P.O. Box 9350 Minneapolis, MN 55440. Please allow 30 days for a response.  
If you are a California resident under 18 years old and a registered user, you can request that we remove content or information that you have posted to our website or other online services. Note that fulfilment of the request may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal (e.g., if the content or information has been reposted by another user). To request removal of content or information, please email content@cheapcaribbean.com.

**Web Beacons**  
We employ a software technology called tracking pixels (a.k.a. Web Beacons) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Tracking pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, tracking pixels are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by tracking pixels to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

**Social Media Widgets**  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CheapCaribbean.com.

**Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Questions or Suggestions**  
Please direct all questions or comments regarding this privacy policy to CheapCaribbean.com, Inc, 2003 South Easton Road Suite 100 Doylestown, PA 18901. 

This Web site may provide links to external Web sites maintained by individuals or organizations external to CheapCaribbean.com, Inc. Once you access information that links you to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the Web site containing the information you have linked to.
